(Beverley:)Now, how could you not tell me
you were in a relationship...
(Beverley:)...with this lovely,
charming young woman?
-Heh, heh. Thank you.
-You're welcome.
(Beverley:)Is it because she's uneducated,
trapped in a menial service position?
(Penny:)What the hell happened
to lovely and charming?
(Leonard:)How come you didn't tell me that you
and Father were getting a divorce?
(Leonard:)How come you didn't tell me
you had surgery?
my dog died?
[EXHALES STUTTERING BREATHS]
(Beverley:)What I hear you saying...
(Beverley:)...is that you want a more intimate
mother-son relationship.
(Sheldon:)I do.
(Beverley(gives him an uncomfortable hug):)There. It's late. Now, go to bed.